

PRODUCT OPERATIONS MANAGER

Details

Jakarta Indonesia 6285868568139 mahardisetyoso@gmail.com

Links

Linkedin

Github

Skills

Data Clean-ups

Data Analysis

Microsoft Excel

Python

Leadership Skills

Project Management

GIS Software

Active English

Hobbies

Reading, Coding,

Languages

English

Profile

Passionate with Data Analysis, Product Operational Management, Geospatial Technology, Business and Leadership ways. Have been in Geospatial Industry for almost 8 years. Early adopter of Python and R, but fluent in Google Spreadsheet. Active person, problem solver, and always have the willingness to be challenged or learn something new.

Employment History

Product Operational Management - Map Ops, GRAB, Jakarta

MARCH 2018 - PRESENT

- Working closely with Product Manager, Program Manager and Country Stakeholder regarding daily basis product operational, product or service launching and technical support.
- Dealing with several project regarding POI, Routing and Geofence service.
- Perform day to day project management, technical support, business case analysis and team management.
- Responsibble for both Country and Team OKR.
- Early adopter for both Python and R, here is my <u>github portfolio</u> and <u>website</u> <u>profile</u>
- Passionate with Geospatial Technology, Data Analytic and Project Management

Business Executive, PT. Datascrip, Jakarta

NOVEMBER 2016 - NOVEMBER 2017

- Responsible to achieve team OKR for selling Surveying and Geospatial equipment.
- Actively engage with Corporate stakeholder as part maintain business partner relationship
- Perform day to day basis sales operational activity, problem solver and product knowledge update.
- Set planning for monthly and yearly plan for achieve sales target

GIS Assistant, Indonesia Forest Service Ministry, Jakarta

FEBRUARY 2016 - NOVEMBER 2016

- Responsiblle to perform analytical and map production for ministry.
- Day to day basis map production operational, paperwork documentation and material presentation.
- Perform analysis forest regarding deforestation issue, analyze forest fire impacted areas, and take part in forest boundary policy.

GIS Operator, EARTHLINE, Jakarta

AUGUST 2014 - OCTOBER 2015

- Perform day to day map production operational basis.
- Collaborate with sales team to create business partnership by take part in defining areas of working using geospatial software to produce in price quotation.
- Must able to operate GIS Software and perform problem solver character.

Education

Bachelor Degree, Universitas Gadjah Mada, Yogyakarta

AUGUST 2008 - DECEMBER 2013

Graduated with 3.2 GPA

Specialized in Geospatial Analysis and Mobile Mapping

Courses

Creative Problem Solving Thingking, Splendens Era PLT

NOVEMBER 2022 - NOVEMBER 2022

Root Cause Analysis

DECEMBER 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

Power BI, Microsoft

OCTOBER 2022 - OCTOBER 2022